在09年的春天 我本来被请去设计\n歌利亚国家银行的新总部大楼
the spring of 2009, I'd been hired to design\na new headquarters for Goliath National Bank.
我是很希望把我的专业意见\n放进这个项目里面
And I was eager to add as much of my voice\nas an architect into the plans as possible.
沐浴在前厅自然光线下的木质横梁
Wood beams bathed in\nnatural light in the atrium.
他们一定会喜欢的!
They're going to love it!
不过唯一的麻烦 就是这位叫Bilson的人
There was only one problem,\nand his name was Bilson.
木头? 自然光?
Wood? Natural light?
不行
Uh, no.
自然光会提醒员工 \n外面的世界有他们的家人和朋友
Natural light reminds the workers that there is an\noutside world where they have family and friends.
我们不想让他们有这种思想
We want to crush that.
你披星戴月 你起早贪黑
You show up in the dark,\nyou go home in the dark,
你要整天呆在黑暗中
you spend your whole\ndamn day in the dark.
我想听听Lily的声音了
I need to hear Lily's voice.
谁让你走的?
Who said you could leave?
Bilson 抹杀我所有的创意
Bilson was killing every\noriginal idea I had.
有一天 GBN换走了他 另外组织了\n一个专责小组来监测我的工作
Then one day, GNB took him off the project and\ncreated a new task force to oversee my designs.
突然间 所有事情都变了
Suddenly, everything changed.
我们会建一个天台禅修花园\n用作静思场地
We'll have a rooftop Zen\ngarden for quiet contemplation.
同时我们会大堂建一个倒影池 \n让本地的小朋友在那里许愿
We'll have a reflecting pool in the lobby\nwhere local children can come to make wishes.
新GNB大楼将会是一个
The new GNB-- a\nplace of work...
一个可以称为家的工作场所
that you can call home.
谢谢 还有...
Thank you, and, um...
欢迎回家
welcome home.
好...好...
My...
我的事情进行的很顺利 \n直到有一天在电梯里
Everything was going great,\nuntil one day in the elevator...
啊 对 我是 Ted 没有...
Uh, yeah, it's Ted. No, no, no, no, no.
我没有批准过更改GNB总部的蓝图
I did not approve that change for the\nblueprints for the new GNB headquarters,
我作为总建筑师 而且才30出头
for which I'm the head\narchitect at only 30 years old.
对 我是单身而且向慈善团体捐款
Yes, I'm single and I give to charity.
但是跟这个有关系吗?
What does that have to do with anything?
好的 再见 市长先生
All right. Good-bye, Mr. Mayor.
你知道这通电话是装的吧?
You know that was a fake\nphone call, don't you?
知道 我还知道GBN新总部大楼的项目\n上个月就被砍掉了
Yes. And I also know that the new GNB\nheadquarters project was scrapped last month.
险些成功哦
Nice try.
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季 第18集
How I Met Your\nMother Season04 Episode18
来看看斯嘉丽・约翰逊 \n去奥斯卡的模样
Check out Scarlett\nJohansson at the Oscars.
如果我可以跟名人上床 \n她一定是斯嘉丽・约翰逊
If I could nail any celebrity, it\nwould definitely be Scarlett Johansson.
热情 有才华 而且显然有严重恋父情结\n不然不会拍那么多伍迪・艾伦的戏
Hot, talented, and nobody does that many Woody\nAllen movies without serious daddy issues.
如果要我和名人上床 她会是Lily
If I could nail any\ncelebrity, it would be Lily.
她是我的女神
She's the star of my heart.
我的话我选休・杰克曼
For me, it'd be Hugh Jackman.
说到名人 我真说不清想要谁
You know, I don't know. Celebrities?
他们总喜欢玩些奇怪的性爱招式 相信我
They're into some really\nweird sex stuff. Trust me.
为什么你会知道的?
How would you know that?
说这个虽然有点尴尬 但是我...
This is embarrassing, but I...
曾经跟过一个名人回家
I went home with a celebrity one night.
天呐 真的吗?
Oh, my God! Seriously?
是啊 他想跟我玩点奇怪的东西 \n我转头就走了
Yeah. He wanted to do this really\nfreaky thing with me, so I left.
就这样 故事说完了
That's it. End of story.
不行不行 这故事没完
No! No. Not end of story.
我要知道时间地点人物 说清楚一点!
I need to know who, what,\nwhen and in where! Spill it!
宝贝 先别激动 \n你不知道吞进去多少空气了
Baby, um, please settle down.\nYou're swallowing too much air.
在你说下去之前 我感到受宠若惊 \n但严格来讲我不是名人
Before you go any further, I'm flattered,\nbut technically, I'm not a celebrity.
还有 上次我戴面具只是开玩笑而已
Uh, and plus, for the last time,\nI put the mask on as a joke.
行了 Barney 不是你
Okay, not you, Barney.
那...他是谁?
Okay, who is it?
很好...看你让Lily打嗝了
Oh, great. Now, you\ngave Lily the hiccups.
好吧 不过我不会说太详细
Okay, I won't tell\nyou anything specific.
嗯 我只是想说他出生在加拿大 \n不过你们肯定认识他
But, um, all I'll say is he is Canadian-born,\nbut you definitely know this guy.
还有他带我去他家 \n是说让我看看一件特别的收藏品
And he got me back to his place by offering\nto show me a very unique collection.
你说的收藏品是什么意思?
What do you mean "collection"?
就是有些人爱收藏邮票或者硬币之类的东西
Well, you know how some people collect,\nlike, stamps or coins? It's like that.
但是我不会说他收藏什么
But I'm not telling.
起码告诉我们他想做什么奇怪的事
Well, at least tell us the\nweird thing he wanted to do.
我不清楚在美国怎样叫它 \n我只知道加拿大的叫法
Well, I don't know what you call it in the\nStates, but we have a name for it in Canada.
看 我已经说太多了
Look, I've already said too much.
一个神秘的名人 他收藏神秘的东西
So a mystery celebrity,\nwho collects a mystery item,
邀请你参与一个神秘的加拿大性爱招式
asked you to do a\nmystery, Canadian sex act?
- 对\n- 说出来！
- Yes.\n- Tell us!
好好 我会说的
Okay, I'll tell you.
前提是你把前三个部分都猜对
But only if you guess\nall three parts correctly.
- 这简直是不可能\n- 没错
- Well, that's just impossible.\n- Exactly.
- 我完全不知道加拿大的性爱招式啊\n- 我知道
- I don't even know any Canadian sex acts.\n- I know.
你应该有"狗拉雪橇式""阿尔伯达毛皮陷阱式"\n还有"加拿大骑警式"
Well, you got your "Sloppy Dog Sled," your\n"Alberta Fur Trapper," your "Full Mountie..."
为什么你会知道这些东西?
How do you know all these?
"加拿大性爱招式组织网" 右边上角那书签
Canadiansexacts. org. It's\nbookmarked on the top right.
- 还是个组织?\n- 对 他们是非营利性组织
- Dot org?\n- Yeah, it's not for profit.
他们只希望让别人得到些信息
They really just want to\nget the formation out there.
嗨  Ted
Hey, Ted.
我刚刚有了一段很奇怪的对话
So I just had the weirdest conversation.
一位在GNB工作的女士说 \n建新大楼的项目已经在上个月被砍掉了
This woman at GNB told me that the new\nbank building was scrapped last month.
简直是胡说嘛 对吧
That's crazy, right?
等等 这是什么表情
Wait, what? What was that look?
我们要告诉他吗?\n我不想让他知道
Should we tell him? I\ndon't want to tell him.
- 我觉得我们应该要告诉他\n- 我们不告诉他
- I think we should tell him.\n- We're not telling him.
没什么特别的表情嘛
There was no look.
哥们 倒底怎么回事?
Guys, what the hell?
好吧 也是时候让你知道真相了
Okay. It's, it's time\nthat you know the truth.
几个星期之前 \nBilson叫我们进去他的办公室...
A few weeks ago, Bilson\ncalled us into his office...
几周之前
a few******\nWe're scrapping the plan\nfor the new GNB headquarters.
我们要砍掉建新GNB大楼的项目
经济衰退太要命了
This recession is killing us.
我们要节省不必要的开支
We're cutting anything nonessential.
我们将会在半年一次的圣克罗伊岛静养时 \n做很多艰难的决定
We're going to have a lot of tough choices to\nmake at the bi-quarterly retreat in St. Croix.
唉 Ted肯定会崩溃的
Man, Ted is going to be devastated.
用好朋友的身份告诉他就没事了
Not when he hears it\ncoming from his best friend.
- 我要告诉他?\n- 我要告诉他?
- I have to tell him?\n- I have to tell him?
你应该告诉他\n他是你最好的朋友
You should tell him.\nYou're his best friend.
我不是 你才是他最好的朋友
Am not, you're his best friend.
不是我 你才是...
Am not, you're his best...
- 我不是...\n- 小声点 他来了
- Am not...\n- Crap, here he comes.
谁 那白人还是那个亚洲人?
What, the white dude\nor the Asian fellow?
看 我都不怎么认识他
See, I barely know the guy.
- 嗨 Ted 咋了?\n- 最近怎么样?
- Hey, Ted, what's up?\n- How're you doing?
我有点失落
I'm frustrated.
每每我把些新意念放进设计的时候 \nBilson总是对我泼冷水
Anything innovative I put in my designs,\nBilson just hacks out with a machete.
我很讨厌跟这种人汇报
I hate having to answer\nto a guy like that.
- 你应该放弃这个项目\n- 你应该完完全全放弃这个项目
- You should drop the project!\n- You should totally drop the project!
- 太不值了\n- 就这样说定了啊
- It's beneath you!\n- Then, it's settled!
送给Ted Mosby人生新一章  \n愿和风抚背--助你行 愿坦途涌现--胜迎您
To Ted Mosby's new chapter! May the\nwind be at your back, and may the road...
你们在开玩笑吗 \n他们才刚刚炒了我事务所另外一名建筑师
Are you kidding? They just laid\noff another architect at my firm.
我是说Bilson是讨厌 \n但是没有这个项目我可能会失业的
I mean, Bilson's a pain, sure, but, without\nthis project, I'm probably out of a job.
对 当你说起项目其实很有趣因为
Right. Um, it's funny that you\nmentioned the project because...
你干的棒极了
You're nailing it!
兄弟好好干
Keep up the good work, buddy!
你今天的头发和牙齿很漂亮
Your hair and teeth\nlook fantastic today.
就像钻石一样闪闪发光
You're shining like a diamond!
谢谢 我就是需要这些鼓励
Thank you. I needed that.
好吧 我是时候上去工作了
All right, I'm going to head\nupstairs and keep working.
我要想想怎样说服Bilson \n让我在那黑暗的门廊加点木头
I got to find a way to introduce\nsome wood into Bilson's dark atrium.
你们知道我的意思
I think you know what I meant.
- 这是什么意思?\n- 什么啦?
- What was that?\n- What?
我有一个想法
I have a thought.
无论任何情况我们继续\n为Ted的事务所多付两个月设计费
Okay, we're paying Ted's firm for two\nmore mths of design work no matter what,
看能不能瞒住他 让他继续工作
so couldn't we just let him\nkeep working and not tell him?
他今年够多事了 \n我们就让他多开心一阵子吧
He's had a rough year. Let's let the\nguy be happy a little while longer.
Marshall 你的提议是一个很复杂
Marshall, what you're\nsuggesting is an elaborate,
时间很长而且非常沉重的承诺
long-term lie that requires\ntremendous commitment.
像你这样的正人君子肯定不能胜任
A nice guy like you can't pull that off.
- 我当然可以了\n- 对我撒撒谎试一试
- Sure I can.\n- Lie to me right now.
好 我有一艘太空船
Okay. I have a spaceship.
- 你的太空船用什么燃料?\n- 算了 我没有太空船
- What kind of fuel powers your spaceship?\n- Okay, I don't have a spaceship.
不行 你要坚持你的立场
No! Stand your ground!
如果有人质疑你 \n就编更多的谎话来分散他们的注意
If someone questions you, distract them\nfrom the original lie with more lies.
这样 让我示范一下\n我有一只小马 问我问题
Here, let me demonstrate. I\nown a pony. Ask me a question.
好
Okay.
啊 你的小马是什么颜色?
Um, what color is your pony?
当我买"蒲公英"的时候 \n她是一只深栗色马
Well, when I first got Dandelion,\nshe was a deep, chestnut brown,
但不幸的是她的马厩就在化工厂附近 \n工厂污染了附近的饮用水
but, sadly, her stable is located near a chemical\nplant, which contaminated the drinking water.
时间长了 她就变成了病态的灰白色
So over time, she's turned\na sickly, grayish-white color
就连兽医也束手无策
and there's nothing that\nthe vet can do to fix her.
天呐 这太惨了
My God! I'm--\nThat's horrible.
"蒲公英"会好起来吗?
Is Dandelion going to be okay?
好 行了 你很在行嘛
Okay. All right. You are good!
"蒲公英"跟本没病 是不是?
Dandelion's not even sick, is she?
那大楼真没有了? 而且你们真对我撒谎了?
So the building's really\ndead and you guys lied to me?
我们 我们只是想保护你
We, we just did it to protect you, Ted.
我真不能相信
I can't believe this.
我刚刚被两个好朋友忽悠了\n而且懵然不知
I just got screwed by my two best\nfriends and I didn't even know it.
在加拿大这叫"鬼祟的雪犁"
In Canada, that's called\na "Sneaky Snowplow."
那大楼是我的梦想作品 但现在它没了
am job, and now, it's just gone.
Ted 真的很遗憾
We're so sorry, Ted.
我想喝点酒
Yeah, I need a drink.
可怜的 Ted
Poor Ted.
我把话题转回加拿大做爱招式\n是不是很无情呢?
Would I seem heartless if I switched\nus back to Canadian Sex Acts?
- 也不是\n- 我惊讶你能等这么久
- Not at all.\n- I'm surprised you waited this long.
这"双手磨冰机"是什么动作?
What the hell is a "Two-Hand Zamboni"?
就是说 一个裸体女人双手套上冰鞋
Let's just say, the only thing the\nwoman is wearing is skates on her hands.
那"马尼托巴奶袋"呢?
A "Manitoba Milk Bag"?
这动作类似"芝加哥胡子"\n不同的地方是下面的人是穿滑雪装
Okay, it's like a "Chicago Mustache," but the\nperson on the bottom is wearing a snowsuit.
那"纽芬兰龙虾陷阱'呢
A "Newfoundland Lobster Trap"?
不知道 也不想知道 \n那帮纽芬兰人太疯狂了
Don't know. Don't want to know.\nThose Newfies are out of control.
好 好 我来猜第一次
Okay! Okay, I'm going\nto make my first guess.
好啊 但是你要猜中是谁 \n用的什么招式 收藏了什么东西
Okay, but I'll only tell you if you correctly\nguess the person, the act and the collection.
好 我猜是布莱恩・亚当斯\n(80年代崛起的著名摇滚歌星)
Okay, I'm going to go. Bryan Adams.
他收藏棒球明星卡
He collects baseball cards,
然后他想做是"油脂皮筏艇"
and he wanted to do a "Greasy Kayak."
不对
No.
Wayne Gretzky(冰上曲棍球明星)\n古董风火轮玩具车 "蹲坐的爱斯基摩人"
Wayne Gretzky, vintage Hot\nWheels, a "Squatting Eskimo."
错
Nah-uh.
基弗・萨瑟兰 \n纪念版小酒杯 还有是"粘连烙饼"
Kiefer Sutherland, souvenir shot\nglasses, and a "Sticky Flapjack."
不是
No.
要是那招 我不会拒绝的
That I would have done.
等一下 如果他们真的停了这个项目
Wait. Wait, if they pulled the\nplug on the project a month ago,
为什么还要我每个礼拜都跑去\n见新总部项目的委员会?
why have I been going in once a week to\nmeet with the New Headquarters Task Force?
很明显的是你不能去找Bilson
Well, obviously you couldn't\ncome in and pitch to Bilson.
其实 那个委员会是我们编造的
So, we... invented the task force.
问题只是如何组成这个小组
Then it was just a question\nof putting together the team.
你记得资本风险部副总Roy Waterman吧
You know Roy Waterman, Vice\nPresident of Capital and Risk?
实际上他是...勤杂工Roy
He's actually... Roy the janitor.
抱歉 Roy 你想不想赚点外快?
Excuse me, Roy. How'd you\nlike to make a few extra bucks?
我这次要脱到啥程度?
How naked do I have to get?
Louisa Mendoza
固定资产部的执行副总裁?
Louisa Mendoza, Executive\nVice President of Assets?
实际上她是... 午餐服务员Louisa
She's actually... Louisa the lunch lady.
Louisa 我想要你帮我个忙\n但你不能跟别人说
Louisa, I need ur help with\nsomething, but you can't tell anybody.
我不会说英语
*******
没错 这是个天大的秘密
Exactly. This is a big secret.
西班牙语是怎么说"秘密"的?
How do you say "secret" in Spanish?
来点肉丸子吗?
********
啊 对 小丸子
Ah, yes. Albondigas.
这是我们之间的秘密小丸子
This will be our little albondigas.
嘿 能不能给我  盛点肉丸子?
Hey, can I, uh, have a\ncouple meatballs, please?
还有Arthur Nasmith \n企业投资部那个古怪的神人?
And Arthur Nasmith, the eccentric\ngenius guru of corporate investments?
实际上他是...
He's actually...
他其实是疯狂的街头艺人\n15大街上表演一个人的乐队
Crazy Arty, 15th\nStreet's own one-man band.
抱歉 能跟你聊聊吗?
Excuse me. Do you have a minute to talk?
这个嘛 由我的助理Reginald安排我的行程
Actually, my assistant, Reginald,\nmakes all my appointments.
我们还拉进来几个实习生\n付给每个人50块钱
We rounded out the group with a few\ninterns and paid everyone 50 bucks
让大家对你的设计表现出极大的兴趣
to act super interested\nin what you were saying.
Reginald
下周可别再给我揽这种活了啊
Reginald, get me out\nof this for next week.
这可以说是我职业生涯里最有灵感的设计
That was some of the most inspired\ndesign work I've done in my entire career.
我那么的兴奋
I was so excited.
Alex Trebek 采用"迟钝的守门员"式\n喜欢收集豆豆公仔毛绒玩具!\n(益智游戏节目主持人 老头一名)
Alex Trebek, a "Musty\nGoaltender," Beanie Babies!
- 不是\n- 该死!
- Nope.\n- Damn it!
等等 \n这就可以解释Louisa那时的反应了
Wait. So that explains the\nthing that happened with Louisa.
- 干得好 伙计 \n- 很好 很好!
- Good job, buddy.\n- Nice, nice!
听着 Louisa 我们之间的互相吸引\n要不要更进一步呢?
Listen, Louisa. What are\nwe going to do about this?
别假装你听不懂我在说什么
Don't act like you don't\nknow what I'm talking about.
我知道你也是有感觉的
I know you feel it, too.
管他呢
What the hell.
不 不行
******
我已经跟Barney先生订婚了
********
管他呢
************
人生苦短
******
不! 不! 不 不能这样做!
No! No! No, this is wrong!
天啊 我怎么能和评委会的人混在一起!
For God's sake, you're\non the task force!
你们还有什么想说的吗?
Is there anything else\nyou want to tell me?
还记得你在GNB垒球队中当三垒手吗?
Well, um, you know how you played\nthird base for the GNB softball team?
记得
Yeah.
根本没有GNB垒球队
There is no GNB softball team.
我们租了块场地 雇佣了一帮人\n让他们把你捧成英雄
We just rented out a field, rounded up a bunch\nof guys and told them to make you the hero.
那么我赢球后绕场一周也是场骗局?
So my game-winning walk was a lie?
很抱歉 Ted 我们知道你很快就会\n丢了这份工的 我们只是--
We're sorry, Ted, but we knew that\nyou'd be out of work soon, and we just--
我们只是想让你觉得好受一点
we just wanted to make you feel good.
你知道 朋友就是这样的
You know, that's what friends do.
对彼此撒谎?
Lie to each other?
有时吧 为了照顾彼此的感受
Sometimes, yeah, to protect\neach other's feelings.
放P! 你不该对朋友撒谎
No way! You never lie to your friends.
我对你可是至始至终的诚实
I would never not be honest with you.
真的? \n在喜剧俱乐部即兴自由表演的那次呢?
Really? What about that open\nmic night at the comedy club?
你们喜欢我嘛 伙计们?
Are you like me, folks?
你们有没有想过有多少种鱼类?
Have you ever thought about how many\ndifferent kinds of fish there are?
还有那些鱼的名字
And the names of those fish.
让我们来瞧一瞧
Let's, uh, let's take a little ride.
鳟鱼 对吧? 鲟鱼\n我想不是 伙计
Trout. Am I right? Sturgeon.\nI don't think so, pal.
鲑鱼 我要再说一遍 鲑鱼
Salmon. I'm going to\nsay that again, salmon.
有谁会认为这是个好名字啊 对吧?
Who thought that was a good idea, right?
鲈鱼\n这个家伙知道我说的啥
Bass. This guy over here\nknows what I'm talking about.
大比目鱼 多谢大家 晚安
Halibut. Thank you, good night.
- 我表现如何?\n- 哦 太棒了 很有趣啊
- How was I?\n- Oh, you were great. Really funny.
你萧杀了...大家美妙的周四之夜
You killed... everyone's Thursday night.
暂停
Time out.
你们不喜欢那个鱼名的笑话?
You didn't like the fish list?
那太糗了!你这是照着念了一长串的鱼名
It was horrible! You\njust read a list of fish.
但是... \n你们都证明了我的观点 对吧?
Anyway... you guys just\nproved my point, okay?
你们骗我是为了照顾我的感受
You lied to me to protect my feelings.
这根本是两码事!
This is completely different!
我浪费了1个月的时间在一个取消的项目上
I just wasted a month of my\nlife working on a dead project.
这段时间我完全可以给我的公司揽些新活
That's time I could've spent trying\nto bring my firm new business.
但是 明天早上我去上班
Instead, I'm going to go\nin there tomorrow morning.
我可能就被炒了
I'm probably going to get fired.
最好的情况也不过是\n我的老板在众人面前对我大发雷霆
Best case scenario, my boss is going\nto ream me out in front of everybody.
在加拿大 我们叫那个 Sas...
Back home, we call that a Sas...
- 萨斯卡通图腾柱\n- 没错
- Saskatoon Totem Pole.\n- Yes.
这上面有
It's on here.
早上好 骗子混人
Good morning, lying bastards.
在我去上班等着被炒鱿鱼之前\n还想骗我一把吗?
Anything you want to lie about before\nI head off to work to get fired?
- 这件衬衣不错 \n- 你真混蛋
- That's a nice shirt.\n- You're the devil.
Ted 如果我告诉你\n我们帮你在GNB拿到了一个新项目
Ted, what if we told you that\nwe found you a new project at GNB
由你来重新设计20楼的某一部分呢?
where you would be redesigning\npart of the 20th floor?
这是个谎言\n而且很拙劣
Well, if that's a lie,\nit's an incredibly dull one.
我具体要干什么呢?
What exactly would I be doing?
这就是第18层楼的E.T.R房间
This is the 18th Floor E.T.R.
事实上 Bilson想要一个这样的房间\n往上2层 我们那层
Basically, Bilson wants a room just like\nthis, only two stories up, on our floor.
等等 什么是E.T.R.?
Wait, what's an E.T.R.?
是雇员中转室
It's the Employee Transition Room.
什么意思?
What does that mean?
恩 这里是上级和雇员一起交流看法的地方
Well, it's a space where a supervisor and\nan employee engage in a knowledge transfer
关于即将发生的职业模式的转变的看法
about an impending\nvocational paradigm shift.
这是雇员被炒的地方
People get fired in here.
太可怕了
That's horrible.
你们干嘛需要一个特定的房间\n来炒员工啊?
Why do you need a room\nspecifically for firing people?
GNB觉得员工需要一个安全舒适的环境\n来应对这个突变
Well, um, GNB feels that people need a\nsafe, secure space to deal with the news.
没错 在这里人性之恶显露无遗
Yeah. It gets pretty real in here.
所以我很不情愿的接下了\n设计炒鱿鱼房间的任务
So I reluctantly agreed to design\na room where people would be fired.
但我坚决要有自己的设计
But I was determined to make it my own.
那么 当你离开这个辞退办公室时
Now, when you leave the dismissal space,
你就会进入我所说的"平静重生"的长廊
you'll exit into what I'm calling\nthe Rebirth Tranquility Hallway.
在这里 将会是一个舒适的椭圆形休息室 \n里面有训练有素的心理辅导员
Here, you'll find a soothing oval\nchamber with a trained grief counselor.
就在这 在"重新来过'喷泉的后面
It's right here, past the\nNew Beginnings Fountain.
就是这样
And there you have it.
跟那个暗无天日的囚室不同\n这是孕育重生的场所...
Instead of a drab, dark prison\ncell, a nurturing womb...
给予你新的生命
birthing you into a new life.
- 我喜欢这个\n- 真的?
- I love it.\n- Really?
- 没错 干得好 Ted\n- 谢谢
- Yeah. Nice work, Ted.\n- Thank you.
你能把这些创意也加入到\n现在18楼E.T.R室去吗?
Can you add some of these touches to\nthe existing 18th Floor E.T.R.as well?
- 当然\n- 很好 咱们来瞧瞧
- Absolutely.\n- Great. Let's take a look.
好吧 那么我觉得这面墙...
Okay, so I'm thinking this wall...
- 你被炒了!\n- 什么?
- You're fired!\n- What?
我想要这样的房间! \n一模一样高两层而已!
I wanted this room! This\nexact room two floors up!
- 但是...\n- 你被炒了!
- But...\n- You're fired!
现在 给我滚出去
Now, get the hell out of here.
嘿 甜心
Hey, honey.
Rush乐队的一员 采用"蒙特利尔牛肉派"式\n收集超级英雄的午餐盒
Anyone from the band Rush, a "Montreal\nMeatpie," and superhero lunch boxes.
不是
No.
好吧Rick Moranis 采用Rerse Rick Moranis式\n犹太老古董\n(喜剧演员及配音员)
Okay. Rick Moranis, The Rerse\nRick Moranis, antique Judaica.
- 不是\n- 我放弃了
- Nah-uh.\n- I give up.
我都猜了3天了 我-我-我玩够了
I've been guessing for\nthree days. I-I-I'm done.
如果我注定猜不到 那就算了
If that means I never\nget to know, so be it.
- 好吧\n- 告诉我们! 告诉我们!
- Fine.\n- Tell us! Tell us!
- 好吧 你们真想知道啊?\n- 没错!
- Okay, you really want to know?\n- Yes!
但是你们不能外传
But this information\ndoes not leave this table.
哦 天啊 我太紧张了
Oh, my, God. I am so excited.
- 我要读了 \n- 读吧
- I'm going to read it.\n- Read it.
- 我要读了\n- 读吧
我要读了 开始了
I'm going to read it. Here we go.
"冷酷的雪地鞋 老国王克兰西式\n Harvey's 餐厅的托盘"
"The Frozen Snowshoe. Old\nKing Clancy, Harvey's trays."
了解了吧?
Right?
我都不知道这些词什么意思
I don't know what any\nof those words mean.
这些词中的某个就是那个名人?
Is one of those supposed\nto be a celebrity?
对啊 谁是老国王克兰西?
Yeah, who the hell is Old King Clancy?
不 这不是人名 是性爱招式
No, that's not the\nperson, that's the sex act.
跟"萨克拉门托高领毛衣"式一样\n不过是用枫叶糖浆
It's the same as a Sacramento\nTurtleneck, except with maple syrup.
那么这个名人是Harvey Straze?
So the celebrity was Harvey Straze?
不 那是他收集的东西\nHarvey's餐厅的托盘
No, that's what he\ncollected. Harvey's trays.
就是那种你在Harvey's餐厅吃饭\n看到的经典的橙黄色的托盘?
Those classic orange trays you\nget whenever you eat at Harvey's?
那个餐厅啊?
The restaurant?
哦 拜托 你们沿着横贯加拿大的公路行驶
Oh, come on, you're road tripping\ndown the Trans-Canada Highway,
在Milverton和Wawa的路上你们饿了\n你们将去哪儿觅食 嗯 ?
you get a hunger on between Milverton and\nWawa, where you gonna strap on a feed bag, huh?
Harvey's餐厅啊 \n卖出不下12,000份食物呢!
Harvey's. Over 12,000 served!
那么这个名人是...
So the celebrity was...
冷酷的雪地鞋
The Frozen Snowshoe.
哦 天啊 ! \n你们没听说过冷酷的雪地鞋么?
Oh, my God! You guys have never\nheard of The Frozen Snowshoe?
他是加拿大最出名的职业摔跤运动员啊
He's only the most famous\nprofessional wrestler in Canada.
02年他在Kamloops纪念赛上打败了\nReckless Rick Rogers后 我遇到了他
I met him after he defeated Reckless Rick Rogers\nin the Kamloops Memorial Arena back in '02.
经典的一战
Classic match.
你是说这个冷酷的雪地鞋邀请你
So you're saying The Frozen\nSnowshoe invited you back
到他家去看Harvey's餐厅的托盘
to his place to look at Harvey's trays,
并叫你一起嘿咻老国王克兰西式?
and asked you to do an Old King Clancy?
没错
Exactly.
我是说真的 你们不能告诉别人
And I'm serious, you cannot tell anyone.
好吧 我不再打嗝了
Well, my hiccups are gone.
也许永远不会了
Possibly forever.
加拿大! 你又来了
Canada! You did it again.
你就连这样的事情都能那么损
You even found a way to ruin this.
为什么? 为什么你居然算得上一个国家?
Why? Why do we let you be a country?
嘿 老大 老大
Hey, mister mister.
你不是该在楼上\n设计你那伟大的美妙的E.T.R.?
Shouldn't you be upstairs\ndesigning your big, fancy E.T.R.?
- 我不干这个项目了\n- 什么?
- I'm off the project.\n- What?
Bilson炒了我
Bilson fired me.
你不是在开玩笑吧
You're kidding me.
这意味着你在公司会怎么样呢?
So what does this mean\nfor you at your firm?
会被开吗?
Are you going to get laid off?
- 事实上 我辞职了 \n- 为啥?
- Actually, I just quit.\n- Why?
因为我不想再为无良的顾客工作了
Because I can't work for big,\nheartless corporate clients anymore.
当我对着你们的"委员会"介绍自己作品的时候\n我真的是在做我职业生涯中最有灵感的事
When I was pitching to your "task force," I\nwas doing the most inspired work of my career.
另外 你们这俩傻瓜提醒了我\n不给像Bilson这样的人卖命
In a way, you idiots reminded\nme how much fun my job can be
我的工作将会多有意思 所以...
when I'm not answering to the\nBilsons of the world, so...
我辞职了
I quit.
- 他们炒了你 对吧?\n- 没错 长官
- They fired you, didn't they?\n- Yes, sir.
但是我得到了不错遣散费\n而且我做出一个重大决定
But I got a sweet severance package\nand I've made a big decision.
我要开自己的公司
I'm going to start my own firm.
- 哇 伙计 \n- 太振奋人心了
- Whoa, buddy.\n- That's exciting.
在这样的经济形势下?
In thieconomy?
你不是疯了吧?
So you're not mad?
实际上 我还有点感谢这一切
As it turns out, I'm grateful.
那么你和Bilson后来怎么样了?
So how'd it all go down\nbetween you and Bilson?
既然他提出了职业方式转变的建议
Well, after he proposed a\nvocational paradigm shift,
本人发表了即席演讲并使用了\n"四管齐下"的做法 让他跪地不起
I made an impromptu presentation using a four-pronged\napproach that really brought him to his knees.
- 搬起椅子砸他?\n- 没错
- Hit him with a chair?\n- Yep.
这才像我兄弟
That's my boy.
2002年 英属哥伦比亚省
****
还有这个 \n是我开车从Milverton去Wawa的路上拿到的
And this one, I got on the\ndrive from Milverton to Wawa.
真是让人过目不忘啊\n冷酷的雪地鞋
That's pretty impressive,\nThe Frozen Snowshoe.
别 我们是朋友\n叫我"小鞋"就行
Please, we're friends.\nJust call me "Shoe."
请坐
Have a seat.
那么 小鞋...
So, Shoe...
你介不介意给我...
How would you like to give me...
老国王卡兰西式的嘿咻?
an Old King Clancy?
我想你该走了
I think you should go.